(Leonard:)Okay, let's try it this way.
What if this People magazine thing
is the best Raj is going to achieve?
- I had not considered that.
- Mm-hm. Come on.
(Sheldon:)I often forget
other people have limitations.
(Sheldon:)It's so sad.
- He can feel sadness?
- Not really.
It's what you and I call condescension.
Now, when we go in there,
let's show Raj that we're happy for him.
(Sheldon:)But I'm not.
(Howard:)Well, then fake it. Look at me.
(Howard:)I could be grinding on the fact that
without my stabilizing telescope mount...
(Howard:)...he never would have found
that stupid little clump of cosmic schmutz.
(Howard:)But I'm bigger than that.
(Sheldon:)Fine. What do you want me to do?
(Leonard:)Smile.
(Howard:)Oh, crap, that's terrifying.